♪ Please lock me away ♪
♪ And don't allow the day ♪
♪ Here inside where I hide ♪
♪ With my loneliness ♪
♪ I don't care what they say ♪
♪ I won't stay
in a world without love ♪
♪ Birds sing out of tune ♪
♪ And rain clouds
hide the moon ♪
- Me?
- ♪ I'm okay ♪
♪ Here I'll stay ♪
♪ With my loneliness ♪
♪ I don't care what they say ♪
♪ I won't stay ♪
♪ In a world without love ♪
♪ So I wait ♪
♪ And in a while ♪
♪ I will see
my true love smile ♪
♪ She may come,
I know not when ♪
♪ When she does, I'll know ♪
♪ So, baby, until then ♪
♪ Lock me away ♪
♪ And don't allow... ♪
Beautiful gown, darling.
♪ Here inside... ♪
Thank you.
♪ With my loneliness ♪
Fabulous.
♪ I don't care what they say ♪
♪ I won't stay
in a world without love ♪
Who are you wearing?
Eloise Turner.
Eloise T, of course.
E.T.
Ellie Turner.
♪ So I wait... ♪
♪ I know not when they come ♪
♪ I know not
when they come ♪
♪ I know not when they come ♪
♪ I know not
when they come ♪
♪ I know not when they come... ♪
It's good news, isn't it?
Eloise, post!
♪ I know not when they come... ♪
- Ellie?
- Coming!
Well, what does it say?
I'm going to London.
I knew you would be.
I'm going to London!
I'm going to London.
♪ Wishin' and hopin'
and thinkin'... ♪
You sure
I can take all of these?
I got you hooked on them.
I can't deprive you now.
Do you have enough space?
Hmm?
Don't you need socks?
Socks.
This was one of the first times
your mum and me went to London.
God, the shops.
We used to look
at all the clothes.
Liberty. Selfridges.
Carnaby Street.
The snooty shopgirls knew
we couldn't afford anything,
but they didn't know
we could copy it.
Take it.
No, I can't, Gran.
Bring her up when I'm settled.
We'll have dinner at the
Criterion, like in the photo.
We didn't eat there.
Couldn't afford to.
Just took a picture outside
and went to a Wimpy.
When I'm a big-time
fashion designer, we'll go.
Deal?
I don't think Wimpy still exist.
You know what I mean.
I know how much you want this.
It was her dream, too,
but it's not
what you imagine, London.
Gran.
You've got to look out
for yourself.
- I know.
- But I'm gonna say it anyway.
- There are lots of bad guys.
- You've got to be careful.
- There's lots of bad people.
- I'll be careful.
They're bad apples.
I'm scrappy. I can take 'em.
I'm just saying,
London can be a lot.
It was too much
for your mum, perhaps,
and she didn't have your gift.
My gift?
She didn't feel things,
see things like you do.
I... I worry you'll get
all overwhelmed again.
Gran, it's... it's not just
that I need to do this for me.
I really want to, for her.
And maybe it won't be so bad.
Maybe up there, I won't be
reminded of her so much.
Okay.
Besides...
I haven't even seen Mum in ages.
Bye.
You'll call?
You know I will.
And if it all gets
too much in there,
you'll tell me?
In the city?
In here.
Please don't do that
to yourself.
Don't do it to me, okay?
I love you.
Oh, Ellie.
I want us both to be there.
I won't let you guys down.
You never could.
♪ Don't throw your love away ♪
♪ No, no, no, no ♪
♪ For you might need it ♪
♪ Someday ♪
♪ Don't throw your dreams away ♪
♪ No, no, no, no ♪
♪ Keep them another day ♪
♪ For you might need them ♪
♪ Someday ♪
♪ Don't throw your love away ♪
♪ No, no, no, no ♪
♪ Don't throw your love away. ♪
- Charlotte Street, please.
- My pleasure, darling.
First time?
I visited once
with my mum, but I was small.
- It looks so different now.
- It changes fast, all right.
But don't you worry, love.
It's still the same old London
underneath.
Good.
What brings you down, then?
I'm studying.
London College of Fashion.
So, you're a model?
No.
I design clothes.
Well, I want to. I mean...
I want to be a designer.
Yeah, but you could be
a model, couldn't you?
You got the legs for it.
So, what's in
Charlotte Street, then?
Uh, student housing.
It's all girls in that building?
If all you supermodels are
gonna be in Charlotte Street,
you'll see plenty of me,
don't you worry.
You might have found
your first stalker.
I'll get out here.
Oh, no, it's a couple
more streets, love.
No, I haven't got enough cash.
Oh, I'm sure we could sort
something out, sweetheart.
Plus, it's not good
round here at night
for young girls on their own.
I want to go to the shop anyway.
Please yourself.
Excuse me.
Can I help you?
Uh, sorry.
Hey, do you want a hand?
Fine.
You don't look fine.
Well, I am.
- Are you Eloise?
- Yeah.
Yeah, you-you look
like an Eloise.
Well, Ellie.
I'm Jocasta.
Did they spell your surname
wrong or something?
Oh, no, I've just decided
to drop it because I feel like
it's way more singular
to be known
by just your Christian name.
You know, like,
so famous in your work
that you can actually
just go by Kylie.
- Minogue?
- Jenner.
Oh.
Okay, bad example, but...
how many Jocastas do you know?
None.
Exactly, babes.
You don't mind I snagged
the bed by the window, do you?
- No.
- If we don't end up throttling each other,
we could maybe talk about
switching next term.
Yeah.
- So, where are you from?
- Uh, Redruth.
It's in Cornwall.
I'm sorry.
You know, Cornwall,
in the countryside.
No, no, I-I heard you, babes.
I'm just, I'm sorry.
Uh...
what about you?
Manchester originally,
but I, uh,
moved down here in my gap year.
Uh, I had an internship
at an atelier in Savile Row.
Oh, wow. I've just been in
Redruth making my own clothes.
I had a hunch you made that.
Yeah, this is Bouchra Jarrar.
Before she sold out
and moved to Lanvin, obviously.
- Smoke?
- No.
Is it allowed in here?
Oh, I-I just took
the batteries out of the alarm.
I can go outside if you really
have a problem with it.
No.
- No, it's fine.
- I tried vaping.
I just think it makes you look
like so much more of a cunt.
Yeah, totally.
So, what does your dad do?
Uh, I don't know him.
Oh, tell me about it.
- And your mum?
- My mother's dead.
Well, I knew we'd find
some common ground eventually.
Yeah, I was only 15
when she died.
What about you?
Seven.
Oh, wow, that is young.
Although I guess
it's maybe easier at that age.
Not that it's a competition,
though, is it?
Ooh, fresh blood!
Oh, my God, wow, is that
a bloody Bouchra Jarrar?
Oh, good eye.
Yeah, well, before she sold out
and moved to Lanvin, obviously.
- Yeah.
- Obviously.
Oh.
Oh, this is my roomie, Eloise.
Hi.
Yeah, she literally made
the outfit she's wearing.
How amazing. All of us
turn up in our Sunday best,
and she's here
rocking her own design.
I'm thinking we should call her
Brass Balls Ellie.
And what will we call you?
Oh, well, by tomorrow morning,
you'll know me only
as Hurricane Jocasta.
Ooh. So you guys know
each other from before?
Oh, yeah, we go way back.
What is it, like 15 minutes?
Yeah, something like that.
We're in the Dead Mums Club.
- Oh.
- Fuck leukemia, am I right?
- That's awful.
- Yeah.
It's pretty shit.
I'm not gonna lie.
But, I don't know, I feel like
it kind of fuels my work.
- So...
- Mm-hmm.
What happened to your mum?
Uh, she wasn't well... mentally.
She... she killed herself.
Sorry.
We shouldn't have asked.
It was a long time ago.
- You're, like, so brave.
- So brave.
Yeah, I had a-a great-uncle
commit suicide... hung himself.
Oh, God.
So, yeah, I know exactly
what it's like.
Also so brave.
- So brave also.
- Yeah.
Mm.
First rodeo, Ellie?
Got to mark
your territory, babes.
- Ooh.
- Oh.
Time to break out the big guns.
Let's really get on this bitch.
Do we really want to be
hungover on our first day?
Oh, hush.
That's future you talking.
You know what, fuck her.
You've got to live
in the now, girls.
So, hos...
...to Soho.
To Soho.
Come on, Ellie. Keep up.
You're gonna love it!
Let's go!
I dated an Irish guy twice.
Well, like, the-the same guy
but, like, two separate times.
- Oh.
- Yeah. Yeah.
And, yeah, he was Irish.
Yeah, and, I don't know,
I kind of feel like
I kind of get the culture.
Watch and learn, guys.
And I just love Ireland.
Like, he literally
introduced me...
Um, excuse me, miss.
Um, my dick just died.
Can I bury it in your arse?
- Ew, absolutely not.
- Get away.
That's disgusting.
Oh, you should try
that line on Eloise.
I bet she's complete filth
once you get a few drinks
inside her.
Okay. Okay.
What?
- Oh, come on, play the game.
- Aw. - Ellie.
Freshers...
they're a blessing and a curse.
It's just a bit shit.
I'm just like...
She's such a code beige,
I'm getting these, like,
born-again Christian vibes
off her.
Who, Country Mouse?
She comes to
her first day at LCF
wearing clothes
she fucking made.
Yeah, that was a bit much.
Bringing up
her mum's suicide... I'm sorry,
but, like, who the fuck
does that for attention?
- Yeah, right.
- She's a bit weird.
She's a lot fucking weird.
I'd lay bets on her
slashing her wrists
before Christmas.
You can't say that.
- It's true.
- Jocasta!
Come on. We've got
another three pubs to hit
before the clubs open.
♪ Baby ♪
♪ You don't know
what you're saying ♪
♪ Because you're a victim
of bright city lights ♪
♪ And your mind
is not right... ♪
Get in here.
♪ Baby, starstruck ♪
♪ You're taken in
by the lights ♪
♪ You're so starstruck,
baby, starstruck ♪
♪ Think you'll never look back ♪
♪ Starstruck, baby, starstruck ♪
♪ You know you're
starstruck on me ♪
♪ Baby, you're running around
like you're crazy ♪
♪ You go to a party
and dance through the night ♪
♪ And you'll drink
till you're tight ♪
♪ And then you're out
on your feet ♪
♪ 'Cause you're starstruck... ♪
What are you listening to?
Nothing now.
You actually listen
to this granny shit?
How old are you?
Mate, you can fucking talk.
Didn't you put on that techno
Riverdance shit at The Toucan?
All yours.
Don't pay any attention to him.
- I'm John, by the way.
- Ellie.
Oh, shit.
Uh, this is your can, isn't it?
Have it.
No, no, no, no!
- Yasmine Rogers?
- Here.
- Gemma Boker?
Poppy Porter?
Here.
Eloise Turner?
It's Ellie.
Uh, sorry.
What was the question?
Are you present?
Yeah.
- Serena Lowe?
- Here.
Jack Sharp?
So, how's
my big-time fashion designer?
I'm good. I'm good.
And did you wow them all?
- I don't know, Gran.
- I bet you did.
Anyway, you still
haven't told me
anything about your place.
It's great.
Very modern.
And how's your roommate?
- Jocasta.
- Is she nice?
- Yeah, yeah, she's fun.
- How lovely.
I say pub crawl, round two.
Almost too much fun.
Well, that's wonderful.
I-I thought maybe
you'd need more time
to get used to being around
so many people.
It's not all too much, is it?
No, I'm okay.
I can't wait to come down
and see you.
- When you feel more at home.
- Yeah.
When I feel more at home.
Soho 0827.
Hi. I saw your advert
for a room to rent.
Yes?
Uh, I'd like to rent it.
Do you know Goodge Street?
Uh, no, but I can find it.
Well, it's 8 Goodge Place.
Press the buzzer for Collins.
Just coming, deary.
- Ms. Collins?
- Yes.
It's Ellie.
We spoke on the phone.
Oh, yes.
Room is on the top floor.
I've a few rules.
Don't take smokers.
I don't smoke.
No male visitors after 8:00.
Not a problem.
And no using
the laundry room at night.
It rattles
right through to mine.
- I don't do laundry.
- Eh?
I mean...
I don't do nighttime laundry.
I do do laundry. I'm very clean.
Good.
It's a bit old-fashioned
for some,
but I won't do nothing to it.
If you don't like it,
you can find somewhere else.
It's perfect.
I love it.
Bed, kitchenette, bathroom.
You won't have to worry
about it until the summer,
but then you'll have to
keep the plugs in
'cause all the smells rise up.
How long have you lived here?
Oh, a long while.
I used to work here,
cleaning and such,
back when round here
was a bad spot.
I bought it for buttons
off the old owner.
Must be worth a lot now.
Oh, I could never sell it.
Too many memories.
Yeah.
If I could live any place
and any time,
I'd live here in London
in the '60s.
It must have felt like
the center of the universe.
I hope you know
what a landline is.
Some of your lot don't.
- Course.
- Don't get too excited.
It only makes emergency calls.
Oh, and I hope you like garlic.
Yeah.
There's a French bistro
next door.
Pretty soon, you won't be able
to smell anything else.
So, when you looking to move in?
As soon as possible.
You're not in any trouble,
are you?
No.
No, I just need, uh, an escape.
Oh, don't we all, deary.
What's your line of work?
I'm a student, but I have
a loan and a bursary.
Well, what do you study?
Fashion.
Ah. Interesting.
Yeah. My gran's a seamstress,
and my mum is...
was in the industry, too.
And you're sure you'll be able
to make the rent?
Mm-hmm. Yeah, I'll make it work.
I do ask more
than your average landlady.
I want two months rent
in advance
and two months deposit.
- Okay.
- I've had people
just take off in the middle
of the night. That's why.
Ms. Collins...
...I would never do that.
♪ You're my world ♪
♪ You're every breath I take ♪
♪ You're every move I make ♪
♪ Other eyes see the stars ♪
♪ Up in the skies ♪
♪ But for me, they shine ♪
♪ Within your eyes ♪
♪ As the trees reach
for the sun ♪
♪ Above ♪
♪ So my arms reach out to you ♪
♪ For love ♪
♪ With your hand ♪
♪ Resting in mine ♪
♪ I feel a power ♪
♪ So divine ♪
♪ You're my world ♪
♪ You are my night and day ♪
♪ You're every prayer I pray ♪
♪ If our love ♪
♪ Ceases to be ♪
♪ Then it's the end
of my world ♪
♪ For me ♪
May I take your cloak, madame?
My cloak?
♪ With your hand ♪
♪ Resting in mine ♪
♪ I feel a power ♪
♪ So divine ♪
♪ You're my world... ♪
And are we meeting
a gentleman this evening?
- We are not.
- Oh, so madame is alone?
I am.
Very good.
♪ If our love ♪
♪ Ceases to be ♪
♪ Then it's the end
of my world ♪
♪ End of my world ♪
♪ End of my world for me. ♪
Once again, Miss Cilla Black.
Hello.
You're a gorgeous creature.
- What's your name?
- Sandie.
Care to join
my friends and I, Sandie?
Thanks, but I'm here
to meet the owner.
I am the owner.
Oh, I doubt that.
I'm whatever
you want me to be, Sandie.
What's your poison, miss?
I'm not here to drink, actually.
I want to speak to the owner.
Owner's not in tonight.
What do you want
to speak to them about?
I want to be
your new headline act.
- Where have you played before?
- Nowhere.
Who starts at the Cafe de Paris?
Me.
I can take your name
if you want,
but maybe you should speak
to Jack in the meantime.
Jack?
Over there.
The guy standing
next to Cilla Black.
Brilliant, Cilla.
Honestly, what a performance.
He manages a lot of girls.
Well, hello there.
The bartender said
I should get to know
the handsome fella
standing next to Cilla Black.
You should.
And you are?
The next Cilla Black.
Are you, now?
Well, you know, she started out
as a coat check girl.
You willing to work your way up?
Of course.
What can I get you to drink?
It's Sandie,
and I'd love a Vesper.
James, we'd love a Vesper.
So, what do you do, Sandie?
Well, I sing, of course.
How's your dancing?
Care for a demonstration?
Here we go.
Your thoughts?
You're already a star.
But you could be an old lady
before you get onstage here.
How about I get you a gig
somewhere this week?
- You could do that?
- I could, indeed.
But first,
let me get your Vesper.
- Do I get a dance now?
- Afraid not.
Oh, you looked up for it
just then.
I'm just waiting for my friend
Jack to get my drink.
- Well, I'm sure Jack won't mind.
- I mind.
Now, don't pretend
you don't love the attention.
Is this man bothering you?
I was just asking
our friend Sandie for a dance.
Her card is full right now.
That's all right, old chap.
Don't hog her all night.
You're the only hog
round here, old chap.
Now, don't be a cunt about it.
You can keep your little whore.
What did you call the lady?
She's a slut, mate. Look at her.
Come on.
Least I can do
is drive you home.
Oh, what's the most?
Well...
- Do you know Goodge Street?
- Very well.
I'm on Goodge Place,
number eight.
Madame.
♪ Anyone who ever loved ♪
♪ Could look at me ♪
♪ And know that I love you... ♪
Being here with
all these lights shining on you,
it's the closest most people
ever get to being onstage.
You know, to their dreams.
Not me.
Not you.
I can see you want it.
More than anything.
Well, this is just a taste
of things to come, Sandie.
♪ In his arms and love me, too ♪
♪ Who couldn't be another heart
that hurt me ♪
♪ Like you hurt me
and be so untrue ♪
♪ What am I to do? ♪
♪ Every time you go away,
I always say... ♪
So, I'll see you again?
I hope so.
Tomorrow, 8:00 p.m.?
You know where to find me.
♪ I take you back ♪
♪ Without you, I'd die, dear ♪
♪ Knowing I love you so ♪
♪ Anyone who had a heart ♪
♪ Would take me in his arms ♪
♪ And love me, too ♪
♪ Who couldn't be
another heart that hurt me ♪
♪ Like you hurt me
and be so untrue ♪
♪ What am I to do? ♪
♪ Knowing I love you so ♪
♪ Anyone who had a heart ♪
♪ Would take me in his arms ♪
♪ And love me, too... ♪
Self-portrait, is it?
Hmm?
Self-portrait?
Uh, uh, no.
It's just someone I know.
Yeah. She looks cool.
She is.
- Like that retro style?
- Yeah.
There's just something about
the '60s that speaks to me.
- Yeah. Nice.
- I'm gonna go check this out.
- Jocasta...
- Fine. What?
Ooh.
This is rather retro.
The hickey. Very daring.
So, what did you get up to
last night in Soho?
Out with some guy?
Or-or girl.
No judgments here.
Live your best life, you know.
You should get some arnica
on that, babes.
♪ I've got my mind
set on you... ♪
Hey.
I really liked
what you drew today.
- The design.
- Thanks.
Oh, and, uh...
Ah, you didn't have to.
It's the least I could do.
What's the most?
Uh, I don't know
why I said that.
- I thought it'd sound cool.
- Yeah.
Do you have any plans tonight?
Yeah, I kind of do, actually.
♪ Everywhere I go, you know ♪
♪ Bad luck follows me ♪
♪ Every time
I've fallen in love ♪
♪ You know, I'm left in misery ♪
♪ This time, I really feel ♪
♪ I feel that it's really real ♪
♪ I feel if I put
my mind to it ♪
♪ I feel that
I really could do it ♪
♪ I've got my mind set on you ♪
♪ I've got my mind
set on you ♪
♪ I've got my mind set on you ♪
♪ I know what I got to do ♪
♪ It's gonna take money... ♪
I'm sorry I'm a little late.
"A little" doesn't
quite cover it.
I've got a feeling
you'll forgive me.
♪ I've got my mind set on you ♪
♪ I know what I got to do ♪
- ♪ It's gonna take money ♪
♪ A whole lot
of spending money ♪
♪ It's gonna take hard money ♪
♪ To do it right, child ♪
- ♪ It's gonna take time ♪
♪ A whole lot of precious time ♪
♪ It's gonna take patience... ♪
It's closed.
Not for you.
♪ To do it, to do it,
to do it, to do it ♪
♪ Oh, yeah. ♪
Jack?
What's going on?
An audition.
All right, knock us dead.
♪ When you're alone
and life is making you lonely ♪
♪ You can always go ♪
♪ Downtown ♪
♪ When you've got troubles,
all the noise and the hurry ♪
♪ Seems to help, I know ♪
♪ Downtown ♪
♪ Just listen to the music
of the traffic in the city ♪
♪ Linger on the sidewalks where
the neon signs are pretty ♪
♪ How can you lose? ♪
♪ The lights are
much brighter there ♪
♪ You can forget
all your troubles ♪
♪ Forget all your cares ♪
♪ So go downtown ♪
♪ Things will be great
when you're ♪
♪ Downtown ♪
♪ No finer place, for sure ♪
♪ Everyone's waiting for you ♪
♪ Everyone's waiting ♪
♪ For you... ♪
So, she can sing.
I can't fucking believe it.
I can.
Can't wait
to get back in there.
It's no Cafe de Paris.
It's perfect, Jack. Thank you.
Well, like I said,
least I can do.
Much better than being
a coat check girl.
And we all have to
start somewhere.
Indeed, we do.
Do you think
I should get a stage name?
- What's Sandie short for?
- Alexandra.
Nah, stick with Sandie.
Suits you.
Could do with some new outfits.
Oh, yeah?
Anything else you need?
A manager.
Know anyone?
I think I can manage you.
Just as long as
you're in it for the long run.
Just as long as you're in it
for the long run.
Just as long as
you're in it for the long run.
Just as long as you're in it
for the long run.
Sandie, I'm with you
till the end.
I can't fucking believe it.
Well, it's certainly a surprise.
If I didn't know it was you,
I'd walk
right by you on the street.
It makes you look so grown-up.
Don't you like it?
- I like it if you like it.
- Yeah, I love it.
I'm just glad you're finding
yourself in London, Eloise.
Gran, it's everything
I ever dreamed of.
It's ambitious...
I'll give you that...
but I'm not sure this
vintage fabric will behave.
I think it's gonna be tricky
to work with.
Oh.
I know this is exactly
what it needs.
It needs something radiant
but not too structured.
Okay. Go on.
Well...
It needs to flow.
I like how it drapes on her arms
- and gathers at her sides.
- Her?
So, you imagine the wearer
when you're designing?
When I see someone in it,
when-when I imagine it,
sh-she's wearing the dress.
The dress isn't wearing her.
I hope you were all
listening to that.
Something about the '60s?
It's excellent, Ellie.
- And I like your hair.
- Thanks.
Wow.
Yeah, it really suits you.
Yeah, it does, doesn't it?
Everything was
so well made back then.
We have a Biba dress
in the back.
1967, immaculate condition.
You should try that one, too.
Yeah.
♪ Just give me another chance ♪
♪ This could be a new romance ♪
♪ Heat wave ♪
♪ Heat wave... ♪
Excuse me.
Are you going to pay for that?
Uh, yes. Sorry.
So, that will be 375 pounds.
Seriously?
3-7-5.
Excuse me.
I was just wondering,
are you still hiring?
- Sorry, it's Irish only.
- Oh.
Only joking.
Speak to Carol down the stairs.
You'd think I'd have more sense
than to take a racing tip
from that fella
after all these years, wouldn't you?
What can I get you, love?
Well, I was hoping a job.
Take a seat. You want a drink?
Uh, yeah.
Could I get a Vesper?
This isn't Mayfair, darling.
Have you ever even worked
in a pub before?
No.
But we all have to
start somewhere.
I'll get you a G and T so.
So, what shifts can you do?
Whenever you want.
Excuse me.
Excuse me, love.
I'm talking to you, blondie.
Sorry, I have to be somewhere.
I'm not trying to pick you up,
sweetheart. Don't worry.
I'm not worried.
You look familiar to me.
Who's your mother?
My mother's dead.
I thought she might be.
Most of 'em are.
Get out of the fucking road!
Watch where you're going, girl.
Jesus Christ.
Can I help you?
It's me, Ellie.
So it is.
Look at that.
- You've changed your hair.
- Yeah.
I wanted to go
for something different...
you know, a bit '60s.
You play a lot
of that music, don't you?
Is it too loud?
Not at all,
but what's that about?
It's more my time than yours.
My gran plays it a lot.
Guess I just like the old songs
better than the stuff today.
Music was better, yeah.
♪ When you're alone
and life is making you lonely ♪
♪ You can always go ♪
♪ Downtown ♪
♪ When you've got worries,
all the noise and the hurry ♪
♪ Seems to help, I know ♪
♪ Downtown... ♪
Ladies and gentlemen...
...keep those hands clapping.
Welcome to the world-famous
Rialto Revue.
Now onstage, give a warm welcome
to the exotic,
the alluring Marionetta.
♪ I... ♪
♪ Wonder if one day that ♪
♪ You'll say that you care ♪
♪ If you say you love me madly ♪
♪ I'll gladly be there ♪
♪ Like a puppet on a string... ♪
♪ Love is just like
a merry-go-round ♪
♪ With all the fun of the fair ♪
♪ One day, I'm feeling
down on the ground ♪
♪ Then I'm up in the air ♪
♪ Are you leading me on? ♪
♪ Tomorrow, will you be gone? ♪
♪ I... ♪
♪ Wonder if one day that ♪
♪ You'll say that you care ♪
♪ If you say you love me madly ♪
♪ I'll gladly be there ♪
♪ Like a puppet on a string... ♪
♪ I may win on the roundabout ♪
♪ Then I lose on the swings ♪
♪ In or out,
there is never a doubt ♪
♪ Just who's pulling
the strings ♪
♪ I'm all tied up in you ♪
♪ But where's it
leading me to? ♪
Where's my Sandie?
Come on, night's not over yet.
Open up.
What do you want?
Don't talk daft. You know.
Once again,
show your appreciation
for Cleopatra!
- All right, Jack?
- Enjoy yourself.
Colin.
- Mr. Pointer.
- Well, well, well.
Please.
We were promised a great show,
and show you did.
Show you did.
Thank you.
Maybe we could, uh...
go for some drinks, Sandie, eh?
Just us.
I'm with Jack.
Oh, Jack doesn't mind.
Do you, Jack?
Not one bit.
Sandie.
Sorry, sir.
Sandie, get back here. Sandie.
- Jack, I don't want to do this.
- You told me you were serious
about being a performer, so if
you want to keep doing it,
then these are the kind of men
that you need to keep happy.
- The men you really need to perform for.
- No, Jack.
Everybody else is doing it.
What makes you so special?
- Oi!
- She said no!
We all have to start somewhere.
Sandie, don't be a damn fool!
Sandie!
Listen, love, come here!
No, it's not what I thought.
Sandie,
this is the way it works.
I'd do what
your manager tells you.
Don't want to make me
unhappy, do you?
- Eh?
- Wake up.
You were the one
who wanted this!
More than anything, you said.
You know this is all an act.
You know where
this is heading, Sandie.
Where are you gonna run to, eh?
Home?
This is just a taste
of things to come, Sandie.
Coo-ee.
I know you're not asleep.
Leave her alone!
You know you're not asleep.
You were the one
who wanted this!
More than anything, you said.
What makes you so special?
What makes you
so special?
What makes you so special?
- Ellie.
- Oh, my God.
Ellie.
Hey, what-what are you doing?
- What are you doing?
- Starting again.
Listen. This is a wobble, okay?
It's just a crisis
of confidence,
and I see it all the time.
But you are really
onto something here,
so don't stop now.
Okay?
Tuned to the moon?
Customer.
- Hi.
- Hey.
What do you want?
Well, I heard you work here now,
and I was going for a drink,
so I thought,
kill two birds with one stone.
Just because you seemed
a little upset in class today.
And I thought maybe
I could swing by,
see how you were getting on.
Thanks.
I meant,
what do you want to drink?
Oh, yeah.
- Three Kronenbourgs, please.
- Sure.
Heard you got a new place.
Yeah. I'm in a bedsit.
That's good, right?
It's really something else.
It must be great
living on your own.
Must be.
Why? What's up?
Nothing.
I'm just a bit overwhelmed
at the moment.
London can be a lot.
I get it.
Coming to the city can be
a bit of a nightmare.
Honestly, I'd be lying if I said
I had the best time
in North London so far.
Where'd you move from?
South London.
I'm gonna get these to my mates.
But...
...I know what it's like
to feel like you don't belong.
And I'm a good listener,
if you ever want to talk.
They're meant to talk to you
about their problems,
- not the other way round.
- Mm.
So, how is everything?
You never tell me
anything anymore.
Everything's great, Gran.
Goodbye, beautiful.
I'll see you tomorrow.
Who was that?
Uh, no one.
Look, we're at the pub,
a whole bunch of us, having fun.
We?
Yeah, Hurricane Jocasta.
Everyone, really.
The whole class.
- Something's wrong.
- No.
Ellie, I can hear it
in your voice.
Gran, I really am at the pub.
I'm working here.
Working there? Why?
- I moved out the halls.
- Oh, no. What...
I needed to get
a place of my own.
Did-did something happen?
- Did you see her again?
- No.
No, Mum's not here with me.
Then what is it?
What's wrong?
Please tell me.
Look, I should go back in.
I know you think you have
something to prove,
but it's okay to ask for help.
She didn't.
Gran, I have to go.
- I love you.
- Love you, too.
Everything all right, Ellie?
Or do I call you Eloise,
like the old song?
I don't know that song.
And how do you know my name?
I make it my business to know
all the pretty girls
around here.
All their problems.
Always have done.
You smoke, don't you, love?
No.
Oh, must be thinking
of some other blonde.
Anyway...
...be well.
Was Handsy bothering you?
Handsy?
Yeah.
The man's like an octopus.
Carol says he was a right
ladies' man back in the day.
Probably thinks
he has a shot with you.
Do you believe in spirits?
What kind
of a question is that?
That brown stuff
pays your wages.
I mean...
do you believe in ghosts?
Ghosts? No.
Why?
Are you scared down here?
If this place is haunted by
anything, it's the good times.
When it's empty,
all I hear is the laughs.
Every gangster, every copper,
every red-faced lush
has been in here,
and all those high spirits
have soaked into the walls.
You could probably
get drunk on just that.
Yeah.
Ellie, I love you, girl.
You fit right in.
But you can't sleep here.
Come on,
they're waiting for you!
- Hey!
- Don't touch me!
Oh, shut up, will you?
Leave me alone!
♪ La, la-la-la-la ♪
♪ La-la-la-la,
la-la-la, la-la-la ♪
♪ La-la, la-la ♪
♪ La, la-la-la-la ♪
♪ La-la-la-la,
la-la-la, la-la-la ♪
♪ La-la, la-la ♪
You know how to dance.
You know why you're here.
Get on with it.
♪ You gotta know how to pony ♪
♪ Like a Bony Maronie ♪
♪ And do the jerk ♪
♪ Let's see you work ♪
♪ Wa-Watusi ♪
♪ Like a Lucy Goosey ♪
Hello there.
Thank you.
What's your name?
Alexandra.
That's a lovely name.
Thanks.
♪ La, la-la-la-la ♪
♪ La-la-la-la,
la-la-la, la-la-la ♪
♪ La-la, la-la ♪
- What's your name?
- Alexy.
- That's a lovely name.
- Thanks.
♪ Mashed potato ♪
♪ Alligator ♪
♪ Do the snake ♪
♪ Do the hippie shake ♪
What's your name?
Andie.
That's a lovely name.
♪ Roll over on your back now ♪
♪ I said I like it
like that now ♪
♪ Ah, goodness ♪
- Hey, what's your name?
- Lexy.
That's a lovely name.
Thank you.
♪ Everybody now ♪
♪ La, la-la-la-la ♪
♪ La-la-la-la,
la-la-la, la-la-la ♪
♪ La-la, la-la ♪
♪ Clap your hands now,
clap your hands now... ♪
- What's your name?
- Alex.
No.
What's your real name, love?
I reckon you're
a copper or something.
Do you, now?
So, what is it?
Sandie.
You're too good
for this, Sandie.
Pretty little thing like you,
laying in the gutter.
I'd get out while you can, girl.
You're better than this.
I don't think I am.
Course you are.
Just look in the mirror.
What if I don't want to?
Then maybe
it's too late for you.
No...
Sandie.
Sandie, look at me.
Look at me, Sandie.
Look at me, Sandie!
You know where to find me.
That's a lovely name.
What's your name?
Alexandra.
- What's your name?
- Alexa.
- Andie.
- What's your name?
- Sandie.
That's a lovely name.
- That's a lovely name.
- That's a lovely name!
- Andie. Sandie.
- That's a lovely name.
- That's a lovely name!
That's a lovely name!
Got any plans tonight, Ellie?
Uh, yeah, I'd love to come out.
I haven't even said
what it is yet.
Right.
But you're saying yes anyway?
Yeah, I need to get out
of the house.
Oh.
Well, there's
a student union night.
A Halloween thing.
Don't we have to dress up?
I was gonna go like this.
And you're already in black,
so it's perfect.
Will that be enough?
Well, I was gonna slap
a bit of this on.
Tell 'em I'm a ghost.
So, want to
haunt this party with me?
♪ There's a ghost in my house ♪
♪ The ghost of your memory ♪
♪ The ghost of the love
you took from me ♪
♪ Where our love used to be ♪
♪ Only shadows
from the past I see ♪
♪ Time can't seem to erase ♪
♪ The vision of
your smiling face ♪
♪ Though you found someone new ♪
♪ I can't get over you ♪
♪ There's a ghost in my house ♪
♪ I can't hide ♪
♪ From the ghost
of your love that's inside ♪
♪ It keeps on haunting me... ♪
Hey, do you want to dance?
I might need some alcohol first.
All right, I'm on it.
No need, guys.
Get these down you.
Happy Halloween, lovebirds.
♪ Ooh... ♪
♪ Ooh, ooh ♪
♪ This is the happy house ♪
♪ We're happy here
in the happy house ♪
♪ Oh, it's such fun ♪
♪ Fun, fun ♪
♪ Whoa ♪
♪ We've come to play ♪
♪ In the happy house ♪
♪ And waste a day ♪
♪ It never rains ♪
♪ Never rains ♪
♪ We've come to scream ♪
♪ In the happy house ♪
♪ We're in a dream ♪
Sandie!
♪ In the happy house ♪
♪ We're all quite sane... ♪
El? El!
What is it, El?
♪ Whoa ♪
♪ This is the happy house ♪
I need some air.
♪ We're happy here... ♪
Ellie!
Ellie.
Is there anything I can do?
I don't want to be like this.
Like what?
I just wish
I was like everybody else.
I'm glad you're not.
Do you want to go
somewhere else?
I'm not meant to have guys back.
Oh.
Okay.
So you'll have to be quiet.
Oh.
Okay.
You don't just want
to go to sleep?
No, I really don't
want to go to sleep.
Well, I can keep you up.
Oh, what am I saying?
- Come on.
- I'm coming!
Ellie!
Okay.
Get off me.
Are you okay?
Get off her.
What's wrong?
Get off her! Get off her!
I'm not... I'm not on her.
Who would even want you?
You belong to me!
I own you!
Don't you ever disobey me.
Ellie.
I'm the one
who'll pay, not you.
Ellie, what's wrong?
Who'd have you now, eh?
Eloise!
What is going on in there?
No male visitors!
Who's in there?!
I'll call the police!
Fuck.
Get him out of here!
Where are you gonna go, eh?
Where you going?
Fuck.
Get out! Get out!
Get out!
You know where to find me.
You know
where to find me.
You know where to find me.
Are you okay?
Yeah.
Did he hurt you?
- No.
- You sure?
He didn't hurt me.
We'll talk about this
in the morning.
Sorry.
For everything.
It won't happen again, will it?
No.
I-I'll-I'll pay
for the mirror, too.
We all pay
for a broken mirror, deary.
Ms. Collins.
Did a girl live upstairs before?
Lots of girls have lived here
over the years.
Someone called Sandie?
Lots of girls have lived here
over the years,
and not all of them
with their real names.
Why do you ask?
Did someone die in my room?
This is London.
Someone's died in every room
in every building
in this whole city.
Every street corner, too.
Oh, and speaking of which,
I would have killed
your gentleman friend
last night if I'd caught him,
so count yourself lucky,
broken mirror or not.
Where you going?
Good morning, Ellie.
Oh, something happened
last night.
♪ I walk along
the city streets ♪
♪ You used to walk along
with me... ♪
How's that?
Um, do you think
it's a bit long?
Yeah.
♪ Oh, how can I forget you ♪
♪ When there is always
something there to remind me? ♪
You know where to find me.
Eloise, what's wrong?
Ellie, are you okay?
What the fuck
is wrong with her?
Ellie.
Talk to me.
♪ You'll always be
a part of me ♪
Ellie! Ellie!
Ellie!
♪ When shadows fall,
I pass the small café ♪
♪ Where we would dance
at night ♪
♪ And I can't help recalling ♪
♪ How it felt to kiss
and hold you tight ♪
♪ Well, how can I forget you ♪
♪ When there is always
something there to remind me? ♪
♪ Always something there
to remind me ♪
♪ I was born to love you ♪
♪ And I will never be free ♪
♪ You'll always be
a part of me ♪
♪ Oh, whoa-whoa-whoa ♪
♪ Whoa, whoa, oh... ♪
Where you going?
Watch where you're going, girl.
These are the kind of men
that you need to keep happy.
Then maybe
it's too late for you.
Don't you ever disrespect me!
I'm talking to you, blondie.
This is London.
You look familiar to me.
Did he hurt you?
Just so I've got this straight,
you-you witnessed
the murder last night,
but you believe this was
a vision from the past,
the murder of a young woman
in the mid to late 1960s
by a man you believe
to be her pimp.
Yeah.
You're an art student, correct?
Uh, fashion.
Have you ever taken
any hallucinogens?
Acid, mushrooms, mescaline?
We're not gonna get you
into trouble if you have.
Yeah, I know it sounds crazy,
but I'm not on drugs.
I don't take anything.
You were at a party before.
Could somebody have
slipped you something?
Maybe somebody
bought you a drink?
Get these down you.
Uh, no.
No, it-it... it started
before last night.
When I was sober,
I saw landmarks in my dreams,
details of nightclubs,
places that
I'd never been to before,
and then I saw those details
in real life.
I know something bad happened
to this girl,
'cause I have these visions,
these visions of the past.
Ever since I moved to London,
I keep seeing Sandie.
Th-That's the murdered girl.
Have you only been here
a short time?
A few weeks.
London, well, it can be a lot.
Maybe it would help
if you spoke to someone.
Look, please just listen to me!
Is there a history
of s-schizophrenia
or mental health issues
in your family?
I know who the killer is.
It's her boyfriend,
uh, and her pimp, Jack.
I've seen him
in the present day.
Look, there's this man
I've seen around Soho
who follows me.
The first time I saw him
outside one of
those models places,
he didn't take
much notice of me,
but he did suddenly take notice
when I changed my hair
to the same style
as Sandie's, the murdered girl.
What, this hairdo?
Look... look, my point is
I've seen Jack.
I've seen the killer
as an old man around Soho.
Can you narrow down
"around Soho"?
He drinks at The Toucan.
I think we've got all we need.
And then she says the...
the killer drinks at The Toucan
and-and narrows it down
to me, you
and the whole rest of Soho.
Yeah,
I'm sitting there thinking,
"This is complete bullshit,
darling."
Miss Turner.
Miss Turner, don't go.
I'd really like you
to stick around.
What do I need to do
to convince you I'm not crazy?
I don't think you are.
I just think you need
a bit of help to settle in.
A-A support system.
You've done the right thing.
Please hear that, okay?
And I will look into
Sandie's murder,
and I've got
your contact details,
so if anything comes up,
I'll be in touch.
Thank you.
Though I will say,
in such cases,
especially this old,
it's hard when you don't have
something concrete to go on...
even a last name.
I want to look up murdered
women, uh, missing persons
in the Central London area
from 1960 to 1969.
Aren't you a fashion student?
Yeah. Yeah, it's research.
You're doing some
cool fashion shoots
based on infamous murder sites
or something?
Yeah.
Yeah, that's exactly right.
- Killer.
- It is.
Hey, Ellie, I got your...
Jesus, John!
Why whisper like that?
It's a library.
Right.
I have your stuff.
You ran out.
Uh, left your bag.
Everyone's here,
cramming for the test.
Listen, about last night.
I mean, if I did
something wrong...
No, you didn't.
Sorry, it's not about you.
Then... what is it, El?
You'll think I sound crazy.
Talk to me.
Last night, I saw something.
In the bedroom, from the past.
What did you see?
A girl was stabbed.
There's a girl
that used to live in my room...
Sandie.
The guy that killed her
is still out there.
So I'm looking
for murdered women
and missing persons
from the '60s
to try and find out her name.
And if I don't,
I'm gonna lose my mind.
Maybe I already have.
Feel free to run a mile now.
Listen.
My auntie believes in
all sorts of weird shit.
So you just tell me
how I can help.
Well, I guess you can start
with the next year of boxes:
1966.
Damn. This is just one year?
London's a bad place.
Library
will be closing in 15 minutes.
That was quick.
Fuck this!
Did you see that?
Ashley, she could have
fucking killed her.
It's okay.
It's not fucking okay.
What the actual fuck?!
Security!
Stay here.
Jocasta! Jocasta, wait!
Security!
Stop!
Jocasta, it was an accident.
An accident?
Are you fucking kidding me?
Security!
What happened to me?
Oi!
Where do you think you're going?
You think you can just
walk away?
Leave me alone!
Hey, come back here, you slut!
Get back here, whore!
I'm talking to you, Sandie!
Leave me alone!
Jack?
Jack! Jack!
Jack!
Where the hell have you been?
I've been covering you
downstairs
for the last hour,
for fuck's sake.
Ellie, get down
in that basement, girl.
You've got a customer.
♪ Bum-bum-bum, bum-bum-bum ♪
♪ Every night, I'm there ♪
♪ I'm always there ♪
♪ She knows I'm there ♪
♪ And heaven knows ♪
♪ Bum ♪
♪ I hope she goes ♪
♪ Bum, bum ♪
♪ Eloise ♪
- ♪ I find it hard ♪
♪ To realize that love was in her eyes ♪
♪ It's dying now ♪
♪ She knows I'm crying now... ♪
And here she is.
You know your siren song
is playing?
I just put this on the jukebox,
and lo and behold, you appear.
Carol was worried about you.
Thought you'd gone missing.
I told her no one ever
really disappears.
They're always around somewhere.
- I'm right here.
- Aren't you just?
I'll have a pint
of Numbers, love.
- I hear you were quite the ladies' man.
- Were?
How dare you?
Still am.
You never lose it.
You knew a lot
of the girls round here?
A lot of 'em?
I knew all of 'em.
Sandie?
Who didn't know Sandie?
♪ My Eloise-a ♪
♪ I'd love to please her ♪
♪ I'd love to care ♪
♪ But she's not there ♪
Do I scare you?
No.
I knew all the girls.
Like to think
I looked after 'em.
Had to keep them
in order, too, mind.
Keep 'em in line.
Sandie, she was special, though.
She didn't belong.
I thought she was
too good for it.
But, you know,
at the end of the day,
you all look the same on a slab.
I know what you did.
I've done a lot of things,
Eloise.
You're gonna have to be
more specific, love.
I know what you did to Sandie.
- Do you, now?
- Mm.
Yeah, I saw her.
I see her.
I know what happened.
Well, whatever happened
to Sandie,
she brought it on herself.
But no one deserves that.
Listen.
I know where you live, Eloise.
And I don't know
what you've seen or heard,
but I can tell you
Sandie ended up
exactly where she wanted to be.
Funny you mention her, though,
because the first thing I did
when I dragged myself back
to this miserable smoke
was to look up her old bones.
But turns out some people
don't want to be found.
But you killed her.
You think I killed Sandie?
I know you did!
Ha! I think you'll find
Alex killed Sandie.
Come back.
Nah. I've had enough
of this line of questioning.
You think she was an angel,
but don't be fooled.
I'm recording this.
You won't get away with it!
So what?
I do what I like in this manor.
The police know! I told them!
Like I give a flying fuck.
Look, wait!
When you see Alex
in whatever little hell
she's currently in,
you tell her I said hello.
Oh, my good God.
Jesus.
- What happened?
- He just stopped
in-in the middle of the street.
Oh, Lindsey, you poor bastard.
Call an ambulance, pet.
Now!
And tell 'em
he used to be police.
- That'll make them hurry.
- Right. Okay.
Lindsey?
- He's police?
- Yeah, he's ex-vice.
He used to be a copper in Soho
for years and years,
working the red light district,
and now look at him.
Then his name's not Jack?
Jack?
No, love.
That's Lindsey.
Yeah, he looks very bad.
I reckon you're a copper
or something.
I reckon
you're a copper or something.
Do you, now?
I'd get out
while you can, girl.
Ellie?
Ellie!
I've let you down.
I've let Mum down.
You haven't let anyone down.
- You never could.
- Okay.
Ellie, I don't know
what's happened,
but it's okay to come home.
You haven't failed anyone.
I'll-I'll come and get you
first thing tomorrow.
No, Gran, I can't stay
another night.
Well, uh, I'll get someone
to drive me now.
Ellie?
- Ellie?
- Hello?
Hello?
Look, I have someone
who can help.
- El!
- I'll call you.
Ellie? Eloise?
- Ellie!
- John!
John!
Ellie.
Thank God.
I saw the flashing lights,
and I thought...
I'm scared here.
I'll take you back to yours.
No, I want to go home.
Home, home.
I-I need to get out of London.
Can you help me get
to the train station?
Forget the train.
I'll drive you.
You have a car?
How else am I supposed to get
to North London
from South London?
Right, I'm gonna go in there,
get my things and never see
that fucking room ever again.
Do you want me
to come up and help?
No, better not.
Ms. Collins would probably
kill you if she sees you again.
Maybe if I plead, she might
give me some of my deposit.
Fuck.
If I'm not back in 15 minutes,
maybe come check on me.
Okay.
Ms. Collins, it's me, Ellie.
Just coming, deary.
You look like
you've had a fright.
I need your help.
Just you, is it?
Yeah.
I'll put the kettle on. Come in.
Your music upstairs got me
breaking out my old records.
Oh, I picked up
a letter of yours by mistake.
It's in that pile.
Don't judge me
on the cigarettes.
All that hoo-ha last night
got me going again.
Sorry.
Oh, it's not your fault.
I was always on the edge
of starting again.
So...
How can I help you?
Ms. Collins,
I-I'm really sorry to do this.
I-I didn't want
to be this person,
but I'm leaving tonight.
Oh.
Are you, now?
I'm not having
a very good time here, and I...
I really need to go back home,
and I promise...
I promise I'll pay you
for the mirror,
- but I really need some of my deposit.
- Slow down.
I don't want to beg,
but this has been a disaster.
Hush. Slow down.
Drink your tea.
You went to the police,
didn't you?
About the room upstairs, hmm?
Yeah.
A nice police lady came round
asking questions about you.
About your well-being.
Welfare check, she called it.
Had me worried.
You'd been saying
a girl died up there.
- Sorry.
- Oh.
It's funny 'cause...
there is some truth in it.
I hadn't thought about it
until you brought it up, but...
a girl did die up there,
I suppose.
The young me...
...that came to this big city.
Sandie.
I had hopes
and dreams like you.
I wanted to be a singer.
I wanted to perform.
To act.
Being a whore is a bit like
being an actress, I suppose.
You have to pretend
you're someone else.
Someone that's not you.
I'd pretend
I was somewhere else.
It's too late for you.
That this wasn't
happening to me.
Try and forget all those...
all those men.
Their faces.
I'd blank them out.
I had to.
Make like they were nothing.
So, yes, you could say
Sandie died in that room.
She died in that room
a hundred times.
And then one night...
...the man who put me there...
...the man who put me to work...
...the man who stole my dream...
...well...
...I put a knife in him...
...a hundred times.
And do you know what, Ellie?
Oh, I can call you Ellie,
can't I?
Yeah.
It felt right, Ellie.
All those bastards
who came ringing my bell,
creeping up my stairs,
they sent me to hell, so...
I sent them to theirs.
The papers call them
missing persons.
As far as I'm concerned,
they were already lost.
So they don't know
where they are.
I say they didn't know
who they were.
I was doing everyone a favor.
I wasn't gonna be used anymore.
I wasn't gonna let
this city break me.
I'm so sorry.
Why?
It's not your fault.
No, I mean I understand.
I know what you've been through.
Oh.
Do you, now?
Yeah, I didn't mean to get you
in trouble with the police.
Oh, it's all right.
They think you're mad.
And it's not like
you're gonna tell anyone else.
No. No, I'm not.
Of course not. I-I would never.
No. I mean...
I know you're not
going to tell anyone else.
Oh, don't worry. I'm not gonna
stab you like the others.
I wouldn't do that to you. No.
You're gonna go to sleep.
And everyone will think you
just topped yourself because,
you know, they all thought you
were going to do that anyway.
They're all very concerned
about you.
Bless.
So, you...
just get comfy, and...
you can doze off
listening to some of
that nice music of yours.
No more excitement
for you tonight.
Just you, is it?
Little liar!
No.
Just coming, deary.
What is it?
Um, I'm here to see Ellie.
She's upstairs. Come on in.
Run!
John!
Will you keep it down!
Enough to wake the bloody dead!
Ladies and gentlemen...
Ellie!
...once again,
Miss Sandie Collins!
♪ You're my world ♪
♪ You're every breath I take ♪
♪ You're every move I make ♪
Leave her alone!
♪ Other eyes ♪
♪ See the stars ♪
- ♪ Up in the sky ♪
- Stop!
Stop!
♪ But for me ♪
- ♪ They shine ♪
- Fire!
- ♪ Within your eyes ♪
♪ As the trees reach
for the sun ♪
♪ Above ♪
♪ So my arms reach out
to you for love ♪
♪ With your hand ♪
♪ Resting in mine ♪
♪ I feel a power ♪
♪ So divine ♪
♪ You're my world ♪
♪ You are my night and day... ♪
I'll get you!
Eloise!
♪ Ceases to be ♪
♪ Then it's the end... ♪
Eloise!
Let me in!
Help.
Eloise!
I'm coming in.
Kill her.
Save us.
No.
- That's a lovely name.
- Sandie!
That's a lovely name.
- Sandie! Sandie!
- That's a lovely name.
I'm with you
till the end, Sandie.
You were the one
who wanted this.
More than anything, you said.
I didn't...
I didn't want any of this.
I know.
I saw.
They deserved it.
I know.
I'm not going to prison.
I've been in a prison
all my life.
No! No!
Please.
You don't have to do this,
Sandie.
You can live.
Please live.
You have to let go!
Leave!
No!
You can't save me.
Save yourself.
Save the boy.
Go!
John, get up!
♪ Downtown... ♪
And now, with a collection
that turns back the clock
to those swinging '60s,
this is first-year student
Eloise Turner.
♪ Downtown ♪
♪ Things will be great
when you're ♪
♪ Downtown ♪
♪ No finer place, for sure ♪
♪ Everything's waiting
for you... ♪
And once again, Eloise Turner.
I knew you could do this.
You're a star, Ellie.
Thank you.
That was incredible.
- You really are so brave.
- So brave.
Thanks, guys.
This is where
she'll be, over here.
There she is.
My big-time fashion designer.
That was amazing, El.
Oh, it was.
It really was.
You're amazing.
Thanks.
I'm just so happy I was here to see it.
I'm glad I'm here
to see it, too.
And you don't need me
to say this, but...
your mum would have been
so proud of you.
I know she is.
♪ You came into my life ♪
♪ Like rain upon
a barren desert ♪
♪ One smile,
and I was born again ♪
♪ I felt sure ♪
♪ It wasn't too late ♪
♪ I found strength ♪
♪ To make me go straight ♪
♪ I had love ♪
♪ And threw it away ♪
♪ Why did they lead me ♪
♪ Astray? ♪
♪ For last night in Soho ♪
♪ I let my life go ♪
♪ I never told you ♪
♪ Of some things I've done ♪
♪ I'm so ashamed of ♪
♪ I thought my foolish past ♪
♪ Was over and done ♪
♪ I would prove ♪
♪ I'd make a new start ♪
♪ I tried ♪
♪ With all of my heart ♪
♪ I had dreams ♪
♪ And broke them in two ♪
♪ I'm just not worthy of you ♪
♪ For last night in Soho ♪
♪ I let my life go ♪
♪ Well, hi there, kid ♪
♪ You ain't been around ♪
♪ For quite some little while ♪
♪ You got yourself ♪
♪ A real cute doll ♪
♪ You're living life in style ♪
♪ But, boy, don't get ♪
♪ Above your station ♪
♪ If you don't want ♪
♪ Aggravation ♪
♪ Got a little job for you ♪
♪ This is what you've ♪
♪ Gotta do, boy ♪
♪ That's how last night ♪
♪ In Soho ♪
♪ I let my life go ♪
♪ Don't cry, my baby ♪
♪ As they lead me ♪
♪ Where no love can help me ♪
♪ Don't stay around ♪
♪ To watch me go ♪
♪ Just forget ♪
♪ There once was a time ♪
♪ You were proud ♪
♪ To call yourself mine ♪
♪ I had love ♪
♪ Right here in my hand ♪
♪ Why could I not understand? ♪
♪ For last night in Soho ♪
♪ I let my life go ♪
♪ I let my life go. ♪